The dusk twilight folds us around by the window
Tomorrow a wonderful happiness will come, again
Your eyes shine with the stars
...and my heart in love burns in flames!
Ika
Cuttlefish
Rieko, it's here!
Oven
Kamado
Domino
Nokogiri
Bucksaw
Ri...
He's playing "shiritori", a game in which you have to find new words starting with the last syllable of the previous; to end with a N is forbidden.
Rinia motor kaa
Linear Motor Car
Rieko! Come here, here!
Bread with bean cream
Anpan!
"N"... it's no good!
Fourth course: Hiroki Nakanishi, from Soukai University
Fifth course: Keisuke Yamato...
I can see him! Nakanishi!! Look!
Anpan-man! Ow... yet another N...
Hey "brother"!
Isn't there another word!?
Look... but what are you doing?
Rieko, you should cheer him, too!
Ari
Ant
Ringo
Apple
Goma
Sesame
Manto
Cloak
To...
Tobiuo
Flying Fish
Ready...
By the way, Ami...
Are you sure we can come up here without permission!?
Don't worry.
I'm always watching him from here.
He promised to me...
that he would certainly win for me.
That's why I don't doubt...
Nakanishi Hiroki
He did it!
New Japanese record??
GREAT! Great, Great, Great!
- He's so cool! He's great!!
- Don't touch me, you fool!
- He's sooo great!
- Leave me!
That's....!
Ami?...
Murderer.
Murderer!
Excuse me...?
Yamato Keisuke
Free-Style Swimmer
He will enter Eiizumi high school
as an athlete.
Come, quickly! It's great!
Ninomiya Ami
High Diver
Nakanishi Hiroki
Free style swimmer
Actually record-keeper in Japan
That's how I met her...
Ouch!
That summer.
Kamisagiryo
It is said that in this world...
there are three people who look like oneself.
I'm a pacifist...
And I dislike violence.
so I never kill any living creature.
Perhaps, what she said...
Murderer!
that "murderer" she was talking about...
...was somebody else, who looks like me.
Or perhaps... did I kill someone without knowing!?
Whatever...
It can't be!!
Thief!
She, again!
What happened, Ami?
Pervert!!
N-no, it's not like it seems!
Really, it's not like that!
- An underwear thief!
I was only hanging out the futon as usual!
No, no!!
Really, it's not what you think!
What's going on, Keisuke?
Takeshi Ogata
diving athlete in the swimming club
There's nothing to say, apart that this is a pervert!
Rieko Kinoshita
athletess in the tennis club
chool
I had just noticed that a pair was missing from the laundry and you...
No!!
It just fell here!
Anyway, it's against the rules...
The underwear should be hang inside the room.
It was decided in order to avoid misunderstanding, right?
And anyway...
You're just too rowdy to be girls!!
Masaru Kume
judo athlete, light weight
The laundry, then the cleaning...
and also how you put out the garbage...
you're really making me mad!
You're so disturbing!
...That's all.
My panties!!
Haruko Tanuma
Judo athletess,
high weights
Everybody, come!
Well, for all the people newly entered...
...welcome to the Kamisagi dormitory.
This year they're early...
You know, this morning...
while I was clearing the garbage...
...the cherry blossoms were like "fuwaaa"...
Listen, grammy...
...Mrs administrator Shoji!!
yes, Mrs administrator Shoji,
we don't have time,
after all we are getting scholarship from the university...
we should hurry and go training.
"Rough"
My daughter is in junior high 1...
there are girls who like to hang around all the time...
my daughter likes drawing.
And so she often draws outside...
..."rough" sketches.
That's why I thought...
...that you are "rough".
Every drawing, for as good as it can be...
it always starts with a "rough" sketch.
From now on, you will lay many lines on each other...
you will redo many sketches,
but from all those lines you have to choose your own one.
It's ok even if it's approximate,
it's ok even
It is not necessary to complete by now the rough sketches.
Make more and more drafts.
"Rough"
To be incomplete, that's your weapon.
[ as-sas-sin ]
I'm a pacifist...
...that's why, if someone hates me so much,
...and on the top of that,
I think that I have to spend the next 3 years together with her...
I can't but feel uncomfortable.
#kanjisub@irc.rizon.net
www.kanjisub.com
That's good, that's good!
It's getting higher, higher!
Come, like that! Like that!!
Ok, ok! Come on, the last one!
...The last 5!
Last 5! Oi, spurt, spurt, spurt, spurt!
Go, go, go!
Good!!
Well done, Yamato!
You got a good stroke! Perfect!
The time?
Time?... Ehm, I got both hands busy,
wait a moment...
This is the whistle, the whistle...
Here, now I stopped it!
I just stopped it and it says only one minute! It's so awesome!
EH!? Teacher... so you did it again!?
Yeah... sorry.
It looks like that Keisuke is getting better.
Nevermind that Ogata, just look at here rather.
I never do the twist well.
About that, you should ask Koyanagi... even if she's not so sociable.
Kaori Koyanaghi
Swimming Club Diving Swimmer
Dormitory
A one-day date?
What do you mean?
A Senior Colleague came here and told me to do a ballot.
He said it's the tradition to do so!
The date?
But only one boy is going as a representative.
And they choose a girl randomly, too.
Well, it's up to the luck of the moment.
Oi oi oi! What's this!? What are you doing!?
A one-day date?
ME ME ME ME!
OK, let's start the ballot!!
When I say "go"...
Take one!
Ready...go!
Haruko Haruko Haruko!
Haruko Haruko!
Uwaaa... thank you!
Don't envy me! :)
We won't!
How lucky!
Tell me it's not true!!
Ready... go!
Not me...
I can't beleive it!
M E . . . !?
Hurry, hurry!
Ready, go!
Kamisagi Dormitory
* Traditional One-Day Date *
Date: At 9 in front of the bell tower.
Wh-wHaaAAt!?
Oi!
Wasn't she the representative for the girls?
[ note: sweet steamed bread filled with azuki cream ]
Manjuu
She said that they fought for the ballot.
[ note: sweet steamed bread filled with azuki cream ]
Manjuu?
Rumors say that Ami Ninomiya is the girls' representative.
But in this case...!
...it was non sense to send Keisuke there!!
Listen...
HEY!
If we don't do as it's written here...
we will be punished with extra cleaning hours!
Relax at the Chirorin café.
Ahem...
They said this afternoon it's going to rain!
But yesterday's forecast was wrong...
I wish they were wrong today too.
The forecast is supposed to miss sometimes.
Anyway, even if it rains, it's ok.
It's not like I'm doing this because I like it.
I don't understand the reason.
Don't think that I like to spend my Sunday...
...with a girl who calls me "murderer".
I remember a story
[ note: a joke with "war of Manchu" ]
"The war of the Manjuu"
Do you know it?
No...
A long time ago...
Two stores of japanese sweets.
The Manjuu's war is started?
One of them was called Yamatoya,
the other was called Ninomiya.
Their respective owners
once used to work in the same store.
They were rivals since the time before they opened their own stores
One day, the owner of the Ninomiya store
invented the owl-shaped manju, "Hoho"
and started selling it.
Ho... ho...
But the owner of Yamatoya didn't give up
so he imitated the other and started selling
a horned owl-shaped manjuu.
A beautiful gift for everyone
the original Hehe
Yamatoya
A beautiful gift for everyone
the original Hehe
He he
It revealed to be a great hit
Probably, the customers
thought that the ears were a free extra
He he, Ho ho
So the stores fought again.
Ninomiya, who was preparing the counter attack...
consumed himself too much in the creation of some new product
and ended sick in a bed.
And then, saying his last words "Yamato killed me!"
in the end......
Murderer!
Now you know the truth.
Yes, I did, but...
I don't understand why are you so mad...
It's all about years ago!
After all you don't even know me well.
We never even talk.
It's enough for me to know that you're the heritance of the Yamato's.
And you don't even consider me as a single human being!?
My grandpa was so important to me.
I loved him too...
grandpa.
For example, I always listen to cassette tapes
Everybody asks me "Why the tapes?"
And even if they always make fun of me...
but for me they're my granpa's memento.
At 1 in the afternoon,
you go to watch a movie at the Moody
Announcement: Permanently Closed
Ouch, it's raining...
It looks like the weather forecast...
were right for once.
Oi!
Listen...
who lives here?
W-wait! wait a moment!
I thought she only wanted to take an umbrella...
Hiroki Nakanishi?
Here, the towel.
Thanks.
Is it ok?
Yeah.
Oh... a date?
So one umbrella will be enough, right?
Come on... stop it, brother!
Brother?
Eh!? Brother!?
Don't be loud.
Sorry.
Are you brother and sister?
No, why?
But you called him "brother"...
[ note: "oniichan" means "elder brother" but
is also used as friendly way to call people, not necessary relatives.]
"Brother"...
[ note: "oniichan" means "elder brother" but
is also used as friendly way to call people, not necessary relatives.]
means brother.
[ note: "oniichan" means "elder brother" but
is also used as friendly way to call people, not necessary relatives.]
How do you say...
we are childhood friends.
Come in. I'll prepare a tea.
Yes!
[ note: to call somebody without the suffix -san
or similiar is very intimate]
Ninomiya... why here?
[ note: to call somebody without the suffix -san
or similiar is very intimate]
Sometimes I come to work part-time here...
...when brother is away for his long journeys.
I come to make the cleaning...
He pays me 800 yen per hour.
Do you want to know a good thing?
He said you're a "mysterious athlete".
"actually he's not making any progress, but..."
"he got talent for swimming."
"He's the kind of athlete who suddenly..."
"breaks all the previous records".
Brother said...
The fact is that...
I heard about it.
That once...
that he saved the Ninomiya's.
Don't tell me that you, with the son of the Yamato's...?
ah, so we're all gathered!
The family of the saviour...
the family that was about to collapse...
and the family that wanted to crush another family.
What makes you laugh about this!?
I also heard about what you were saying about me.
Somewhat sounded like compliments to me.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Well, you know...
that you called me...
"mysterious athlete"...
No...
I didn't say nothing like that.
Oh... yeah! ^^;;
Sorry!
What's up?
What's up with you!?
If you got something to say, then say it!
Was it funny?
To look at my happy face while I didn't understand I was being fooled.
What are you talking about?
He never said those things.
Nakanishi.
He never called me...
he didn't even notice me.
Everybody called him "flying fish".
When we attended the same pool, once...
They called Nakanishi the "flying fish".
Whilst my surname was "damedaka".
They joined "failure" (dame) and "killifish" (medaka).
Since then I moved to another club.
Since then I always aimed to be better.
Even in that period
the truth was
I didn't want to make that race.
I
hate you.
Show it in the pool.
Huh?
I don't know what happened...
but the answer is in the pool.
Results come after.
Take it all out.
Why this words all of sudden?
I understand, more or less, what you're thinking of.
As we live in the same small room...
Tie it tight, tight!
Yeah like this!
You fool!
Sorry!
You're an idiot! What are you thinking of!?
I have no such intentions!
Yes sir.
You idiot! Haha.
Well. Did he come?
I'm off.
Ok. Thank you.
Well...
What is that?
As you can see, it's a heartbeat counter!
One of those "pipipi" signal!
As from today, you will have to measure during the training! Got it!?
Both physical and mental care!
We have to reinforce more and more heart, lungs and everything! So in the next race...
He will be the best in Japan!
Professor Sakiyama...
We're aiming at it, too...
Let's do it, all together!
Yes!
Wh-what's that... ah, this!
Yeah, this...
Good, like that! Last five!
Good!
1 Hiroki Nakanishi
2 Keisuke Yamato
Nice one!
OK!
Look here! This way!
It's true that you're a "misterious athlete".
The last time, before the race...
I wanted to act as a break.
But now...
i need to say it
You did well, huh
Anyway you' keep ignoring me.
Not like I care.
But I want to tell you as athlete to athlete.
...even if I've been eliminated in the qualification race.
Anyway!!
You just did your personal record, right?
Well, there's always a 0.4 difference with brother's...
It's true that Nakanishi is 0.4 seconds ahead...
...more important that that, I couldn't tell her yet...!
"sorry"
That's good...
summer vacations are so quiet.
Ehy, why is that girl here, too??
Ah, Kume asked me to invite her.
She puts on airs!!
She's always on her own and never even steps in the dormitory.
...agree?
Yeah.
Turns me down.
Hey, help me!
Ah, all right, sorry.
Hey, help us to carry this stuff!!
Kume! Ogata! Yamato!
YAMATO!?
Did you just say YAMATO!?
Dad...
Who's Yamato??
YOU?
You're Yamato!?
He's just a school fellow, his name is YamaDA!
And... what else?
We're done with the shopping.
Nakanishi, why are you here?
Because I'm worried.
It doesn't look fit in here!
Ami offered it to me...
What's the relationship between you two?
Between you and Nakanishi.
Well...
We're like brother and sister.
A good friend to talk to...
someone I can count on, and am proud of.
And I like him so much!
So you like him...
And what about you, Koyanagi?
Do you have someone...?
...at present?
Yes...
The boy I'm interested in...
is the second fastest athlete in crawl, in Japan.
She sure swims well.
She's my best athlete.
Haha, so it's because the master is good.
...He's the best in Japan, after all.
The wind is arising...
Hey, don't go too far!
Huh? What?
It's time you come back!
I can't hear you!
Ow, it's so noisy!
Oi!
Watch out!
C'mon, hurry!
Catch me! ahah
Call an ambulance!
- Yes!
- Let's go!
Ami!
Ami!!
By by~~e!
See you.
Bye.
It seems like today'll be really hot.
Oh, that's damn true...
Do you think you will be alright?
Yes.
Just to be sure, I was visited once more.
Also the doctor said that there's nothing to worry about.
Is that so...?
Good to hear...
I'm sorry...
that I made you worry.
Hey, Ami
[ note: hitsumabushi: eel fillets cooked over charcoal with
soy flavoured sauce, cut in small pieces and served on rice]
Let's go eat!
today's hitsumabushi.
[ note: hitsumabushi: eel fillets cooked over charcoal with
soy flavoured sauce, cut in small pieces and served on rice]
Eel, eel!
[ note: hitsumabushi: eel fillets cooked over charcoal with
soy flavoured sauce, cut in small pieces and served on rice]
Oh! So cute! What's that?
[ note: hitsumabushi: eel fillets cooked over charcoal with
soy flavoured sauce, cut in small pieces and served on rice]
Oh! So cute! What's that?
Nothing.
You hide it! Let me see!
That's nothing, nothing.
Dinneeeeer!!
Haru, hurry up!
E E L ! !
Eel, eel, eel, eel today!
I don't care if there won't be left for you!
How are you?
Huh?
I don't have something special to say, but...
How are you?
Huh?
Listen...
you can use that.
whisper, whisper... careful...
Go.
...thanks.
Please... just don't fall.
OK, no problem.
I'm oK now.
And you?
I heard that you dived for me the other time.
He sure is fast!
I'll never swim like him.
After all, he's the retainer of the national record.
So why did you dive for me?
Well, you know...
Thank you.
Despite all, you did dive for me...
The pitch is too slow!!
Don't move your head!
oi oi oi oi oi!
No no no no no!
Is this the way to swim!?!?!?
Professor Sakiyama, you sure are positive!
Oh, he just made a personal record!
Huh?
No, it's impos-
IT'S TRUE!!
How come?!?!
How can you be so calm!?
How fool...
Fantastic!
It's all your merit, prof. Sakiyama!
Thank you very much!
It's because you spread this passion...!
Yamato!! Hurry and come to say thanks already! Idiot!
Sincerely, thank you!
Yamato, you're great!
Teacher, I love you.
I knew you can do it, Yamato! Very good!
Let's get married... oK?
Teacher, teacher! So, is it ok?
Cut it out already!
Do you think it's all right to laugh like that?
The situation is critic.
For that..... brother of yours.
I'm not particularly happy.
I'm looking forward to it
...to see which one of them is going to get the support.
I'm not going to miss it!
Yamato... I like you very much, too!
I love you, too, Yamato! thank you, thank you!
Finally the Japanese championship has come!
Oh! "Fifth consecutive victory?"
"Hiroki Nakanishi, Sokai university"
Is this the latest edition?
Here, dad.
Yeah
"The champion"
"Hiroki Nakanishi"
"from Sokai University"
"retainer of the Japanese record"
Keisuke Yamato *new promise*
Yamada, alias...
Yamato.
Damn...
Yamato~~!
Listen, daddy...
Daddy, wai-...
Kamisagi dormitory
Well
Thank you
Here it's oK
The next time we'll meet...
it's on the day of the competition.
Yes
Ah... on that day...
it's not like I'm good at it, but...
I'll  cook the lunch for you, so let's eat together, ok?
"Roba" (donkey)
"Ba"...
Ba... ba... ba...
Babaroa! (bavarian cream)
tsumazuite korondetara
(I stumbled and fell)
Uwaa! It's so late!
tsumazuite korondetara
(I stumbled and fell)
Uwaa! It's so late!
oitekarenda
(and I've been left alone)
Sorry!
oitekarenda
(and I've been left alone)
doromizu no naka wo kyou mo
(and also today, in the middle of mud)
Yes... thank you brother!
yoromekinagara susumu
(the day goes on, even if I stagger)
Yes... thank you brother!
yoromekinagara susumu
(the day goes on, even if I stagger)
Yes... yes, oK!
yoromekinagara susumu
(the day goes on, even if I stagger)
Yes... yes, oK!
yogorechimatta boku no sekai
(my world is so dirty now)
OK, I'm waiting for you!
yogorechimatta boku no sekai
(my world is so dirty now)
uita hanashi nado nai
(I got nothing to be merry about)
shimitsuita kodoku ronri
(the logic of loneliness, sticking inside me)
nuguenaku natte iru
(will never scrape away from me)
A... a...
nuguenaku natte iru
(will never scrape away from me)
A... a...
tamesarete made mo (to the point to try me out)
Anpan
koko ni iru koto wo kimeta noni
(even if I decided to stay here)
Anpan
koko ni iru koto wo kimeta noni
(even if I decided to stay here)
No, no...
koko ni iru koto wo kimeta noni
(even if I decided to stay here)
A... a... a...
koko ni iru koto wo kimeta noni
(even if I decided to stay here)
A... a... a...
jumon no you ni
(like an enchantment)
A... a... a...
jumon no you ni
(like an enchantment)
shikata nai to tsubuyaiteta
(I whispered "there's nothing I can do about it")
Anpanman!
shikata nai to tsubuyaiteta
(I whispered "there's nothing I can do about it")
Anpanman!
tsumiageta mono bukkowashite
(let's make in pieces all we've been piling up)
Anpanman!
tsumiageta mono bukkowashite
(let's make in pieces all we've been piling up)
mi ni tsuketa mono topparatte
(let's trow away all the schemes)
tometonai chi to ase de
(with endless blood and sweat)
kawaita nou wo uruwase
(give some new vigor to the thirsty brain)
ano koro no bokura wa kitto
(at that time, we...)
zenryoku de shounen datta
(...were young men full of energy)
Kamisagi dormitory
zenryoku de shounen datta
(...were young men full of energy)
Kamisagi dormitory
sekai wo hiraku no wa dare da?
(who will open the new world?)
Kamisagi dormitory
asobu koto wasuretetara
(when one forgets how to have fun)
oite karenda
(one gets old and withers)
kokontoko wa shigoto onrii
(now it's all about work...)
waraenaku natte iru
(and can't even laugh anymore)
Keisuke, Keisuke, Keisuke!
Hiroki Nakanishi
heavily injured in a car accident
Ami
Bye bye
Bye
[ note: They're at English lesson ]
...he be of soul who could pass by
A sight so touching in its majesty
This city now doth, like a garment
Ok, who wants to translate until this point?
Do you want the lunch to be warmed once more?
[ amulet for road safety ]
Don't you come to the training?
The teacher is on the rag
he says you don't want to do nothing
The champion can
Keisuke
Do you know what's your weak point?
Try to jump
We're at 10 meters
It's the same height as when we dive.
Hey...
I think I would die...
We always dive from such height
That's why we get mad when we see someone like you,
who retires in his shell!
Shell?
Yeah, the shell!
Every time that something happens,
you always make a face as if nothing were.
and squash your feelings
and close with a shell!
What's up, you're suddenly serious...
That's just natural!
Being serious,
getting angry, crying, suffering
in the reality, there are such things!
You have to take it all out!
You're fighting for a 0.01 second!!
If you don't break this shell and take things seriously,
for as pathetic as it can be,
you have to take it all out!!
Otherwise you'll never be able to win!
Don't touch me!
Now I'm wicked, right?
So you're skipping class again!?
If you got nothing to do, then help me already
By the way...
That... Ogata, who lives in the same room as you
did you know he will be leaving the dormitory?
Announcement to all athletes...
please gather in the main hall...
It's not like I wanted to hide it from you.
I was planning to talk to you about it after the competition.
Is it because... you don't want to be emotional?
Yeah
It's already a long time
that my father is sick.
They say he doesn't have much time left to live.
I got to go back home and take care of everything.
Today it's the last one.
- Excuse me!
You're Ogata and Yamato, right?
Yeah...
Yess!!
- Can we take a picture?
- Can we?
Yeah...
Great!!
Please come here!
Please!
I'm going!
Smile!
Smile, Keisuke
Ok, cheese!
Ogata he . . . .
I was very proud...
even though I said those things to you last time,
to tell you the truth,
when I wrote letters to my family,
I always wrote about you.
I said that you have a great talent.
This is the final dive for the competition
Perhaps, I'll never get a chance to be as excited as today.
As time goes by...
I may also forget the way of diving.
But...
I got the feeling...
that certainly i will certainly
miss this place
Keisuke
I'm...
very proud of you.
Do you want to dive?
From here?
How can I dive for good?
Teach me
It's impossible!
Teach me!
It's not so easy!
Come on,
teach me.
I said it's impossible!
You'll get hurt!
I want to win
not over somebody else
I......
want to win
against what I was "one second" ago.
Am I the only one... who remembers about this?
Keisuke, hurry up and fetch it back!
A long time ago...
"She" made me cry all the time.
I couldn't even swim
and she made me swim to see who arrives first to the other side...
she always told me to dive from high...
all the time, pushing me.
But...
at some point,
for some reason I couldn't meet her anymore
...so I cried again.
Me... the hospital...
on that day...
if only...
if only I didn't phone him...
brother... that injury...
It's all my fault.....
NEXT SUMMER
I'LL BREAK NAKANISHI'S RECORD!!
I'll break it, got it?!
I'll break it no matter what!!
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
(at the subway entrance, hand in the hand)
itsumo no zawameki, atarashii kaze
(the usual noise, a new wind)
akaruku miokuru hazu datta noni
(I thought I would see you of with a smile)
umaku waraezu ni
(instead, I couldn't laugh for good)
kimi wo mite ita
(and just stayed staring at you)
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
(at the time you'll grow up)
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
(I don't want sad songs to overflow you)
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
(there's something I want to tell you, now that we're at the end)
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
(I tried to use different words)
boku wa sagashiteta
(for not saying "goodbye")
totsuzen fui ni narihibiku beru no oto
(the sound of a bell that echoes so suddenly)
aseru boku tokeru te hanareteku kimi
(I'm in a bind [*impatient], our hands untie, you leave)
muchuu de yobitomete dakishimeta nda
(I called your name to stop you, and then hug you)
kimi ga doko ni ittatte boku no koe de mamoru yo
(everywhere you'll go, I'll protect you with my voice)
Ah... it's snowing!
kimi ga doko ni ittatte boku no koe de mamoru yo
(everywhere you'll go, I'll protect you with my voice)
Look, it's snowing!
kimi ga doko ni ittatte boku no koe de mamoru yo
(everywhere you'll go, I'll protect you with my voice)
Look, it's snowing!
kimi ga boku no mae de arawareta hi kara
(since the very first time you showed up in my life)
nanimo kamo ga chigaku mieta nda
(everything looked different to me)
asa mo hikari mo namida mo, utau koe mo
(the morning, the light, the tears, the singing voice)
kimi ga kagayaki wo kureta nda
(you made everything shine, to me)
osoekirenai omoi wo kono koe ni nosete
(I want to put my uncontrollable feelings into my voice)
tooku kimi no machi e todokeyou
(and make them get to you, who are so faraway)
tatoeba sore ga konna uta dattara
(and if by chance it was trough a song like this one)
bokura ga doki ni ita toshitemo
(anywhere we are....)
tsunagatte ikeru
(we'll be able to be united)
Keisuke, a phone call for you.
Oh
Hello, I'm Yamato.
You have to come and see
tomorrow
there's the student championship.
Uwaaaa! Brother!!!
The athlete in the fourth course
Nakanishi, from Sokai University
with 49 seconds and 68---
This sets a new Japan record
I put all myself into it
That accident... wasn't Ami's fault.
"Don't think about it anymore"
I came back to tell her these words.
So---
I can't absolutely lose.
This time---
I want to be the one...
to save Ninomiya from drowning.
That's all.
It was worth
to wait for one year.
Do you really quit?
I couldn't even train for one whole year...
So you quit...
without mastering the twist dive.
We can just say bye bye
if it's her will to quit.
There are two things I'm sure about
that I trained a lot
and that in the meanwhile
I never stopped watching you
Always...
we were always the last two to remain in this pool.
The reason why I could keep on training hard
was you.
I like you.
The supporter's bus is about to leave!
Come on, hurry up!
Ninomiya...
recently...
you've got always the same expression.
What expression?
A sad expression.
...We finally arrived to the last year.
These three years seemed long, but were short
Many things happend
I......
I've been watching you all the time.
And you certainly swimmed.
You kept on swimming.
So that's the only thing I can say:
that your effort wasn't in vain.
Certainly, it will help your back to grow bigger.
Got it?
GO WITH ALL YOUR STRENGH!
Yeeeeeah!
Alright, do your best!
Don't you dive?
If you want to, do it quickly.
I haven't done it for a long time...
so I'm a little afraid.
So you can't dive, huh?
Because your heart is confused,
Thats why you cannot dive.
Confused?
No, really, I'm not...
So what are you doing here?
You don't have time left.
The competition is about to start
Those two . . .
had already made up their minds.
They've decided that today will be the day
But you...
what are you doing!?
This is not the place...
to escape from reality, right?
It's not like... I can't decide.
I......
when I look to oniichan,
I think he's so fantastic.
So why don't you go to support him!?
Why don't you go!?
To support your brother!
After all you love him, right!?
Yes!
I love him so much!
My big brother...
has always been...
since always...
since I was this little...
has always been there for me.
Always with me...
we went out together
we talked all the time
He always protected me...
gave me many good advices...
it's on him that...
I could always count on...
that I'm proud of...
that I love so much...
I . . . .
I will go.
Then...
let's dive together.
Oniichan!
Ninomiya?
Yes, and she told me to give it to you.
Do you want to know...
what did she tell me
that time?
No thanks.
It's not something worth knowing, anyway.
I don't believe that you, Nakanishi, could ever tell me...
something that may distract me before the race.
Huh?
How odd...
Come on...
Huh? And the race?
Don't you go to see?
Do you have some other thing to do?
A heart-break.
That's what it was.
Well, it's going to be all right.
Dumped or be dumped, summer will come around again.
So
I'm going to save Ami.
OK.
Ready
Ah...
Ahhh...
Can you hear me?
I'm Ami Ninomiya.
can you hear me?
Today is friday, august 25
9.25 am
...and 31 seconds... 32...
33...
34...
The temperature is 28 degrees
Sky is sunny, light breeze.
Ah... can you hear me?
I love you.
Ninomiya Ami over and out.
Yamato Keisuke
Yamato Keisuke!
Answer me
I've been physically good, these days, but...
Translation: Jiru-kun
My heart beats fast, I don't know why
Styling: Soshen
ENG editing: furransu
Further Editing, Encoding and everything else etc.: Ko-FI.me/OrangeFlash
Under this burning sun
I suddenly feel such high tension!
I got the nerve now, so...
the distances will vanish at will!
I want to kiss those lips
I get closer to the target
ant take it at once!
"the important is to put words in action"
..and to avoid as much as possible troubles!
But actualy things don't go like that
But I decided, you go first!
always in the essential moment
that whimp starts crying loud
Doesn't make a step out
You're pathetic! What the hell are you doing!?
"I don't care"
"and anyway it's no use"!
But before deciding on your own
you should know that it doesn't matter how you look!
Don't stop your feelings
You can't decide yourself anything you do
and you're always saying spiteful things!
So what do you really want!?
If you're always so half-hearted, you'll never get...
the victory!
how many times did you fall in love!?
Nevermind that and go straight forward
Don't try to change this passive character of yours,
but quit it for good!
Behind every success
there's the shadow of the anxiety!
Yesterday and today it was rainy,
so tomorrow it's gonna be sunny!
It's no use to be so half hearted
I understand it rationally
It's not necessary to think only about the result
Don't cloud off your will
on the line that prolongs a complete love!
There's an eden full of hope and glory.
You have to change the ideal you always aimed to into reality.
Don't be afraid!
Engine to max power!
so what's the most important thing?
You gotta ask to the bottom of your heart
If you try to make one step outside
this is your moment, shout!
make your love explose to the climax
it will pop in yur heart!
don't worry anymore about how you look!
don't stop your feelings!
don't lose your feelings!
Mom!
Mom, look, look at me!
This uniform fits you better than anybody else!
You got the same face as I did when I was young!
Bye bye!
By~~e!
Be a good girl!
OK!
- Hi!
- Good morning!
Takayuki! Your necktie...
It's not straight... do something!
- 'morning
- hi
- Bye
- See you later
It's late, hurry up!
Byeeee!